primaryads.com 2009-06-16

# PrimaryAds - Privacy Policy

---  
  
**Privacy Statement for PrimaryAds.com Effective January 1, 2007**

We respect you and we hold your personal information private.

Kowabunga! has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: PrimaryAds.com

We never disclose your personal information to any third party.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information.

Our site may use cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and unique identifiers (like their social security number). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt out section below. Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected for use as account numbers in our record system.

Our site uses a contact form for customers to request information, products, and services. We may collect visitors' contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the form is used to send orders to our customers. The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.  
  
**Public Forums**  
  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.  
  
**Security**  
  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  
  
**Choice/Opt Out**  
  
We do not provide your personal information, including email address, to any third party.

You will only receive communications from Kowabunga!

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:

You can send email to Aleks.Jagiella@kowabunga.com  
  
**Contacting the Web Site**  
  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact:

Aleks Jagiella  
Kowabunga!  
15550 Lightwave Drive  
Suite 300  
Clearwater, FL 33760  
Aleks.Jagiella@kowabunga.com
